搞什么?
Aah!What the fuck?
这也太离谱了吧!
That was so fucked up, you guys.
前情提要
滚吧 你走人吧
Get out. You're done.
有一个人 你永远无法打败
There's one person you will never, ever defeat.
没了我 祝你好运
Good luck without me.
我们企盼的解决方法
The answer to all our prayers.
一种杀死超人类的病毒
A virus that kills Supes.To make the virus
病毒强大到足以杀死祖国人
strong enough to kill Homelander would evolve it
就会演变成致命的东西
into something super lethal.
一场他妈的全球流行病
Global fucking pandemic.
我就是你 所以我告诉你你想这么做时
I am you, which is why when I tell you you want to do this,
我是在实实在在地告诉你 你他妈的想这么做
I am literally telling you that you fucking want to do this.
喜美子
Kimiko!
法兰奇 病毒不会凭空出现 兄弟
Frenchie, that virus...it ain't gonna cook itself, brother.
我们不会拿莱恩当武器
We ain't turning Ryan into an asset.
他还没准备好 要么我们想办法训练他
He ain't ready.Either we figure out how to train him
要么我们想办法杀死他
or we figure out how to kill him.
停下来 快 停下来
Stop, stop! Just stop.
你的家人不是敌人
Your family isn't your enemy.
我妈不会希望我拍这个
My mom wouldn't want any of this.And that
这就是为何我对这孩子充满信心
is why I got faith in the kid.
一旦他上任 我们需要援引第25条修正案
Once he's in office,we need to invoke the 25th amendment.
谁来处理这一切?我
Who's handling all this?Me.
我他妈的来处理
I fucking am.When Homelander
祖国人把星光追随者们都关进拘留营
chucks all the Starlighters into internment camps,
你也觉得无所谓吗?你对拘留营一无所知
you're cool with that?You didn't know about the camps.
你专心管好枪手就行了
You just focus on the shooter.
确保他六号那天准备就绪
Make sure he's good to go on the 6th.
你没事吧?里面热得像个熔炉
Are you okay?It's like a furnace in there.
该死的变形超人类
Stop!Fucking Supe shapeshifters.
不过不得不称赞智者
Got to hand it to Sage, though.
刺杀任务的完美人选
Perfect choice for the job.
沃特新闻网《今日新闻》
头条 早上好 爱国者们
Good morning, patriots.
今天是一月六日 欢迎收看《今日新闻》
It's January 6, and this is VNN Today.
沃特工作室传来令人震惊的消息
Stunning news out of Vought Studios,
沃特工作室紧急取消了 广受期待的电影
who are canceling the eagerly anticipated film
《训练火车头》 虽然该片业已杀青
Training A-Train, though it's completely finished.
我们意识到该片的盈利前景惨淡
We just realized we'd make more from the write-off.
沃特新发布了强有力的公共服务广告 我们走进幕后 一探究竟
We go behind the scenes of a powerful new Vought PSA.
所有生命都重要 我承担责任
I take responsibility.
我承担责任
我承担责任 承担种族主义的责任
I take responsibility for racism.
最后一条消息 今天国会清点选票
Finally, Congress counts electoral votes today
对即将上任的总统进行核实
to certify the incoming president.
通常是走形式 但鉴于达科塔鲍勃极端的
Usually a formality, Dakota Bob's extreme anti-Supe agenda
反超人类目标 这次绝对不会走走形式而已
has made it anything but.
我们将以有序的方式清点选票 不经辩论
We will count the certificates in an orderly fashion,
议长卡尔霍恩清点选票
with no debate.
清楚了吗?
Is that understood?
如我所说
Now, as I was saying,
核验选票后
after ascertaining the certificates are authentic...
该死的病毒呢 法兰奇?
Where's the fucking virus, Frenchie?
快准备好了
I'm close.
一旦他们敲响木槌
You know, once they bang that gavel,
纽曼他妈的就进椭圆形办公室了
Neuman's one goddamn head pop away from the Oval Office.
还要多久?不大久了
How close?Close-ish.
操
Fuck.
是否有人反对清点阿拉巴马州的选票?
...counting the certificate of the vote of the state of Alabama?
进入超人类事务局的数据库了吗?
Hearing none. The chair advises members of Congress...
我们得尽快查出那个变形者的身份!
没有 我说过 维琪对数据库把控得很严
No, I told you Vicky locked it all down.
还有 拜托你小点声
Please lower your voice.
嘿 嘿
Hey.Hey.
嘿
Hey.
什么事?
He-Hey. What...
你穿的是什么呀?
What the hell are you wearing?
你不喜欢?
You don't like it?
不 我是说 我 我喜欢
No, I mean, I... I love it.
只是 时机对吗?全国即将卷入
It's just, I-is now really the time, with the whole country
极权统治的洪流啊
barreling towards 1984?
我曾祖父出征前的那一晚
The night before my great-grandfather shipped out,
穿上了制服
he put on his dress uniform,
闯入我曾祖母家 在晚餐桌旁
barged into dinner at my great-grandmother's house,
单膝跪下
and got down on one knee.
好吧
Okay.
站起来好吗?
Stand up. Please.
休伊坎贝尔
Hughie Campbell...
你愿意娶我为妻吗?
...will you marry me?
你站在这里 好吗?别动
You need to stay right here, okay?Just don't move.
好的 不要动
Okay.Do not move.
嘿
Hey.
我想我得跪下
Uh, I guess I'm-I'm doing this.
那我也跪下 求婚的是我 好吧
Okay, then me, too, 'cause I'm the one proposing.
安妮詹纽艾瑞
Annie January,
即将发生的事情令我恐惧
I am terrified of what's gonna happen.
但能
But I feel so...
和你一起面对这一切 我深感幸运
...so lucky...that I get to face it all with you.
好 好了
Okay, all right.
所以 总而言之
So, uh, yeah, all in all...
绝对同意 我们结婚吧
hard yes, let's get married.
英雄克星
刚才 太爽了
Wow, that was... that was great.
两根手指有点过火 但是
Two fingers was a lot, but...
对不起 我只是想更爽一点
Sorry, I was just trying to level up.
不 那是 没关系的 很棒
Oh, no, it's... it's fine. It's great.
你要去哪儿?
Where you going?
我们得喝点香槟庆祝
We need some champs to... celebrate.
不能喝冰箱里的柯克兰廉价酒
And...not that Kirkland shit that's in the fridge.
我马上就回来 好的
I'll be right back.Yeah, okay. Yeah.
议员们告知我 堪萨斯州的选票
The certificate from Kansas, the parliamentarians advised me,
是唯一出自该州
is the only certificate of vote from the state,
并附有权威机构认证的选票
and has annexed to it a certificate from an authority...
高压90 低压60
You're 90 over 60.
很低
That's low.
这还用你说嘛
You don't fucking say?
如果你需要任何帮助
You know, if you need any help...
我不需要你的帮助 真的吗?
I don't need your help.Really?
在我看来 你已经 床上拉 床上尿了
Seems to me you are shitting in a bedpan
离入土不远了
and days away from being planted.
你还有什么牌?
And what do you have to show for it?
辛格尔?他玩完了
I mean, Singer... he's as good as dead.
祖国人 他赢了
Homelander... he won.
而你 你说出了病毒的事
And you... you gave away the virus.
唯一一件本可以阻止祖国人的武器
The one fucking weapon that could've stopped him.
但我们会扭转局势的
But we are gonna turn that frown
我的朋友
upside down, my friend.
知道为什么吗?
You know why?
因为你还有我
'Cause you still have me.
你他妈根本就不是真实存在的
You ain't even fucking real.
真是个很有趣的哲学问题
Well, now, that's an interesting philosophical question.
五号造成的肿瘤
See, what is real are the fucking
在你五脏六腑里 大脑里 雨后春笋般地生长着
V'd up tumors that are mushrooming inside your guts and noggin.
超级癌症!
Super cancer.
你有时想要烧死
What is real is that piece of you
地球上每一个该死的超人类
that wants to burn every fucking Supe on Earth.
你觉得自己是怎么 把以西结大卸八块的?
How is it you think you ripped Ezekiel into fun-sized little chunks?
我就是那个赋予你所需力量的人
I'm the one that gave you the juice that you needed.
我可以再做一次
And I can do it again.
只要你履行诺言就行
All you have to do is hold up your end of the bargain.
要我付出什么?
Bargain?
要我他妈的付出什么?
What fucking bargain?
我们破釜沉舟
We go all the way.
毫不留情 拜托 哥们
I mean, come on, champ,
搞点种族灭绝算什么呢?
what's a little genocide between friends?
滚吧 让我安然离世 好吗?
Just fuck off and let me die in peace, would you?
我倒是想
Wish I could.
既然你来了
Since you're here...
行行好 给我点酒喝 好吗?
...be a doll and fetch us a pint, would you?
拜托 别这么刻薄 我他妈的快死了
Come on, don't be a cunt. I'm fucking dying here.
我巴不得你快点死呢
Your dying's been pretty high on my wish list lately.
你来看我 我很感激
I appreciate what you're doing here for me.
我并不是为你而来
Not one bit of this is for you.
那好吧
All right, then.
把手机给我 我们还有工作要做
Give us me phone. We got work to do.
恶心
Disgusting.
该死的 莱恩
God damn it, Ryan.
过来
Come here.
过来 这是命令
Come here. That's an order.
我是你的父亲
I'm your father.
他可不是
Not him.
我永远都是
And I always will be.
马上过来
Come here.Now.
莱恩
Ryan.
莱恩!
Ryan!
精瘦小伙子减肥午餐
嘿
Hey.
要是我就会小心些
You know,I'd be careful with those...
小心那些精瘦小伙子减肥午餐
...those Lean Lad Diet Lunches?
它们会害你长出大块的肾结石
They cause kidney stones the size of jawbreakers.
这家公司被集体诉讼了呢
There's a whole class action lawsuit against them.
过来 不 别他妈碰我
Come here.Don't!Don't-don't fucking touch me.
冷静点 好吗?
Hey, chill, okay?
我需要补充面具能量而已
I just need a little recharge.
我他妈的为什么要杀你妈呢?
Why the fuck would I kill your mother?
得去塞多纳才能杀了她
That requires going to Sedona,
塞多纳那种地方 谁都不该去
and no one should have to go to Sedona.
别读取我的记忆
Get out of my head.
这个?
Oh, this?
今天早上我向休伊求婚了
I proposed to Hughie this morning.
我甚至还给他讲了你曾祖父母的故事
I even told him the story about your great-grandparents.
然后我们就做爱庆祝
And then we fucked to celebrate.
我们肛交了一下下 他喜欢极了
And we did butt stuff.He was so into it.
天哪
Oh, Christ.
这里热得像个熔炉
It's like a fucking furnace in here.
为什么?求婚多棒啊
Why?Don't you just love proposals?
对方脸上满是喜悦
I mean, the joy on the other person's face
他们终于得到了永久的幸福快乐
when they finally get their happily ever after.
你个疯子反社会者
You're a psychopath.Sociopath!
不难预料吧
Which is to be expected, really. I mean,
我几乎不记得自己的样子了
barely remember what I look like.
但我还记得自己的第一次变形
I do remember the first time I shifted, though.
我瞬间就变成了贾米森小姐的样子
One minute I was me and the next I was Ms. Jamison,
她是我的幼儿园老师
my preschool teacher.
我可以看到她过往的每一段记忆
And I could see every memory she'd ever had.
跟她丈夫最好的朋友上床
Fucking her husband's best friend,
在商店里偷唇彩 打学生
shoplifting lip gloss, hitting a student.
但你知道有趣的是什么吗?
But you know what the funny part is?
她觉得做这些烂事都是合理的
She felt justified in doing all those shitty things.
你们都是这样
You all do it.
你们都认为自己做的事合情合理
You all think you're the heroes of your own story.
看看你
I mean, look at you.
比起我们这些肮脏下流的超人类 你更有道德
You're more moral and good and honest than the rest of us
更善良 也更诚实
just wallowing down in the shit.
我不这么认为你就是这么想的 拜托
I don't think that.Yeah, you do. Come on.
读心术 记得吗?
Mind reader, remember?
在选美比赛中
"Wasn't my fault
我是彻头彻尾的混蛋 那并不是我的错 是我妈的错
that I was a total cunt at the pageants, that was Mommy.
必须像吸吮冰棒一样给人口交
Or that I had to suck cock
才能留在超级七人队里也不是我的错
like a fucking popsicle to stay in The Seven. No.
不
No, no, no, no, no.
我是安妮詹纽艾瑞 这不是我的错
I'm Annie January and it's not my fault."
快点 现在就和我一起说
Come on, say it with me now.
我是安妮詹纽艾瑞 这不是我的
I'm Annie January and it's not my...
去你的
Fuck you!
对于我或我的生活 你一无所知
You don't know anything about me or my life.
是吗?那为什么你无法发动超能力呢?
No?Then why aren't your powers working?
最初甚至都没选你 做杀死辛格尔的替罪羊
I mean,you weren't even the original choice to kill Singer,
但你麻烦缠身 一无是处
but you're just such a fucking hot mess,
选你再好不过了
you made it undeniable.
嘿
Hey.
你会被判好几个无期徒刑
You'll have a couple of...non-consecutive life sentences
你可以好好解决自己的身份认同问题
to work through your identity issues.
求你了
Please...Aw.
可怜的安妮
Poor Annie.
求你了 天哪 我是安妮詹纽艾瑞
Please."Oh, God, I'm Annie January
我是唯一的好人
and I'm the only good one."
给
Oh. Here.
正好配那些精瘦小伙子午餐
To wash down those Lean Lad Lunches.
好啦
Okay.
休伊
我给你打了15通电话 我很担心
Oi oi.I've called you, like,15 times. I was worried. I thought...
我不知道 还以为你
I don't know, I thought maybe you were...
是的 我也以为自己死了
Yeah, you and me both.
现在时间有点紧
Look, we're kind of up against it right now.
再过几个小时 选举的验证结果就要出炉了
They're only a few hours away from certifying the election
之后 他们就会对辛格尔采取行动
and then, you know, after that happens they're-they're coming for Singer.
我们需要你的帮助
We need your help.
布彻尔?
Butcher?
年轻时
When I was a lad,
我听说内华达州有个地方
I heard about this place in Nevada.
一家牛排馆
A steakhouse.
女服务员给你上肋眼牛排时 上身一丝不挂
Where the birds get their baps out when they're bringing your ribeye.
好吧
Cool.
我告诉莱尼这事时 他笑得差点背过气去
Lenny nearly pissed himself when I told him.
觉得是他听说过的最好笑的事
Thought it was the funniest thing he ever heard.
我们本想找个时间去一趟
We was gonna go there someday.
说起来
Well...
将死之人想的事挺逗的 不是吗?
Funny what you think about when your time's up, innit?
布彻尔 你在哪里?我可以去找你
Butcher, where are you?I-I can come to you.
我们可以想出办法来
You know, we can figure this out.
休伊 帮我们个忙 好吗?
Do us a favor, would you, Hughie?
去那里
Go there.
替我和莱尼去 好吗?
For me and Len, would you?
你他妈的不能放弃
You can't fucking give up.
你仍然可以战斗
You can still fight.
休伊 我说出自己的请求了
Hughie, I asked you something.
好吧 我会 我会
Fine. I'll-I'll, um...
我会替你们去那家裸体牛排馆
I'll go to the topless steakhouse for you.
感激不尽
Magic.
另外
And, uh...
告诉英雄克星们我很抱歉 好吗?
...tell the Boys I'm sorry, would you?
告诉英雄克星们我很抱歉
Tell the Boys I'm sorry
因为
for, uh...
告诉他们我很抱歉就行了
Just tell them I'm sorry.
再见 休伊
Goodbye, Hughie.
对了
Oh, hey, um,
让涅金给我买杯吉特咖啡店的 焦糖脆饼烤棉花糖冰沙
have Negin get me a caramel pretzel s'more frappe from Jitter Bean.
双份起泡奶油 今天我又累又乏 没什么精神
Double whip. I'm just like molasses in winter today.
天哪 够了 安布尔 谢谢
Ugh, God, that's enough, Amber. Thank you.
早上好
Good morning.
你今早还好 天哪
How are you doing this mor...Oh, God.
不好意思
Excuse me.
我们可以快点结束采访吗?
Can we just make this quick, please?
我今天还有稍微更重要些的事
I have slightly more important things to do today.
嘿 准备 等等 五 四
Yes ma'am, of course.Hey.Stand by. Going in five, four,
三
three...
祖国人和当选副总统纽曼 今天清点选票
Welcome to the show, folks.
欢迎各位收看 今天 我们给大家带来了一个惊喜
We got a real happy surprise for y'all today.
祖国人和当选副总统
Homelander and vice president-elect
维多利亚纽曼!
Victoria Neuman.
非常感谢两位来做嘉宾
Bless both your hearts for being here.
我很乐意为朋友祖国人挤出时间
I'm more than happy to find time for my friend Homelander.
闲话少叙
Yeah, let's cut the BS.
达科塔鲍勃说他会在上任
Dakota Bob says he's gonna pass nutbag anti-Supe laws
一百天内就通过 不合常理的《反超人类法》
in his first hundred days.
作为其副总统 您会如何阻止这种疯狂的举动?
As his VP...
作为超人类社群坚定的盟友
...staunch ally of the super-abled community,
我认为很重要的
I really think that it's important to...
盟友 维多利亚?真的吗?
Ally, Victoria, really?
我们来做嘉宾是要说实话
We're here to tell the truth.
所以 说实话吧
So just... tell the truth.
事实是这样的 真正的问题就是缺乏代表性
The truth is that the real issue here is lack of representation.
我们只是想确定 好吧 你不想说实话
And I want to make sure that you...Fine, you don't want to do it?
那我来说
I'll do it.
维多利亚是个超级英雄
Victoria here is a superhero.
谢谢你的称赞
Thanks for the compliment.
但我认为事实是 我们都想成为英雄
But, like, I think the truth is we all want to be heroes,
可我实际上并不是个
but, um, I'm not literally a su...
糟了
Oh, fuck.
这都是真的
It's all true.
这位纽曼女士已然
Ms. Neuman here has been operating as
以秘密武器的身份 进入了暗深势力集团
a secret dagger in the heart of the deep state,
勇敢地面对意图亵渎我国民主
standing up to the forces of darkness that want to
鸡奸我国幼儿的黑暗势力
sodomize our democracy and our toddlers,
但现在 伟大觉醒的时刻到了
but it is time for the great awakening.
团结一心 沃特力量 各位!
Where we go one, we go Vought, y'all.
我们稍后回来
We're gonna take a quick break...
秘密被说破了 不是吗?
Cunt's out of the bag, innit?
现在有好戏看了
Now it gets interesting.
节目很棒 各位
All right. Great show, guys.
嘿 嘿!
Hey. Hey!
滚一边去 嘿!
Ma'am...Fuck off! Hey.
我一辈子都在努力保守这个秘密!
I worked my whole life to keep that secret.
不过秘密会腐蚀你的灵魂
Well, secrets rot your soul.
你毫无负担了 该感谢我才是 智者说
You're unburdened. You should thank me.Sage said...
去他妈的智者 她早被炒鱿鱼了 听我说
Fuck Sage. She's long gone. Listen to me.
听我说
Listen to me.
我们要改变世界
We are gonna change the world,
维琪 为了我们的下一代 以及他们的下一代
Vicky, for our kids and their kids.
第一位超人类总统
The first super-abled president.
而且你是个女孩子
Hmm?And you're a gal.
我会被弹劾
I'll be impeached.
我们为什么要在乎?
Why would we care?Because I have to
因为四年后我必须再次当选谁说的?
get re-elected in four years.Says who?
《宪法》第二条说的新世界 新规则
Article II of the Constitution.New world, new rules.
现在 你他妈给我闭嘴 听话
Now shut the fuck up and listen.
我们的命运现在已经联系在一起了
Our fates are connected now.
辛格尔已经完蛋了 你他妈的只有我这一个朋友了
Singer's as good as dead, and I am the only fucking friend you've got left.
覆水难收了 美人儿 这水就是你泼出去的
The train has left the station, gorgeous, and you're on it.
你必须得逮捕你公司一半的人 这个国家一半的人
You'll have to arrest half your company. Half the country.
怎么 你以为我没想到那一点吗?我当然想到了
Wait, you think I didn't think of that?Of course I thought of that.
他妈的!
Fuck.
艾诗丽 跟我走 社交媒体上的反应不一
Ashley, on me now.Um, the response on socials has been mixed.
我需要你提交一份清单 列出公司内任何掌握
I need you to make a list of anyone within the company
对我或超级七人队不利信息的人
that has damaging information on me or The Seven...
但主要是我 任何有谈判筹码的人
but mostly me...anyone with any fucking leverage whatsoever.
是马上就交到我手里
Yes.I need this fucking list yesterday.
是 先生
Yes, sir.
好姑娘
You're a good girl.
听起来不太妙 艾诗丽 可不是嘛 艾诗丽
that doesn't sound good, Ashley.Oh, yeah, no shit, Ashley.
对不起 艾诗丽
Sorry, Ashley.
保持秩序!议长卡尔霍恩发言人结束会议
Order!
联席会议的计划已完成
The purpose of the joint session having concluded,
根据参议院 暨国会第一百一十八次会议 联发的第一项决议
pursuant to Senate Concurrent Resolution 1, 118th congress,
议长宣布联席会议已表决
the chair declares the joint session resolved.
突发新闻 辛格尔及纽曼的选举结果已被核验
...certified the election despite the shocking news
选举结果核验完毕 尽管有令人震惊的消息称 当选副总统维多利亚纽曼是超人类
that vice president-elect Victoria Neuman is super-abled.
全国各地均已爆发抗议活动
Protests have erupted all over the country
这下局面完全不同了
as Starlighters...That's the ballgame.
现在人人都有可能攻击辛格尔 法兰奇
Open season on Singer now. Frenchie, tell me you got something.
你最好是成功了没有
You want to try this instead of me?
不然你来试试 我已经尽量加快速度了!
I'm working as fast as I can.
不够快
Not fast enough.
多名抗议者受伤 至少十
Multiple protestors have been injured...
看到这条新闻了吗?
You seeing this?
准备好纽曼的污点信息 防止事态恶化
Get all the dirt on Neuman ready in case we need to go nuclear.
等等 病毒研制得怎么样了?
Wait, wait, wait, wait. What happened to the virus?
没研制出来
There is no fucking virus.
什么?他妈的!
What?Fuck.
好吧 如果我们泄露这些 她会杀了我们 对吗?
Okay, well, you know she's gonna kill us if we leak this, right?
相信我 如果另有选择 我不会这么做的
If I had another fucking choice, trust me, I'd take it.
管不了那么多了
All right, here goes fucking nothing.
嘿
Hi.
不 他妈的!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Fuck!
怎么了?发生了什么?都不见了
What?What happened?It's all gone.
我们掌握的关于纽曼的所有信息 谋杀
Everything we have on Neuman... the murders,
她与艾德加的关系 等一下
her ties to Stan Edgar, everything.Okay, okay, wait a second.
你有备份吗?另一台计算机 或者云端储存!
You got backups, right... another computer or the motherfucking cloud?
你没仔细听 信息不见了
You're not hearing me. It's all gone. The originals,
原件 备份 什么都没了!
the backups, we've got nothing.
那就没法阻止她了
Ain't nothing stopping her then.
只有一个办法了
Only one thing left to do.
法兰奇 你留在这里 再快点
Frenchie, you stay here, work fucking faster.
喜美子 你跟我走
Kimiko, you're with me.
我给你发坐标 你和安妮尽快去那里跟我会合
Listen, Hughie, I'm sending you coordinates. You and Annie,
计划是什么?
meet there ASAP.What's the plan?
进攻是没机会了 现在只能防守了
We fucked up our chance at offense. All we got now is defense.
对于这种对信任的根本性背叛
I am as shocked as you are
我跟你们一样震惊
by this profound betrayal of trust.
在美国 要求别人给你投票之前
In America, you tell people who you are
要告知他们你的真实情况
before you ask for their vote.
正是因为这样 我才呼吁新的自由 公正的选举
That's why I'm calling for a new, free and fair election.
记住我的话
Mark my words,
除非我死了 否则 维多利亚纽曼
if Victoria Neuman becomes vice president,
绝不会成为副总统
it will be over my dead body
因为她派人暗杀我
because she had me assassinated.
我猜你得去 全天候保护辛格尔了 不是吗?
Wow. Guess you got to go take a bullet for the geezer, don't you?
我认为我留在这里更为重要
I think it's more important that I stay here.
你等的那个访客到了
Your visitor's here.
让他进来
Send him in.
伙计 这样肯定不行的
Man, this is never gonna work.
你收到了我的短信
You got my text.
你来了 我很高兴
I'm glad you came.
现在你已经快比我高了
You're almost taller than me now.
这孩子没救了 遗传的力量大得很
There's no saving the kid. He can't escape his own blood.
他们给你吃什么?
What are they feeding you?
希望有点蔬菜
And tell me there's vegetables involved somewhere.
汉堡上有生菜
There's lettuce on the burgers.
我好想你 孩子
I've missed you, kiddo.
听着 莱恩
Listen, Ryan,
我们得严肃地谈谈
we, uh, need to have a bit of a serious chin wag.
你看上去病得很重
You look... really sick.
可不是嘛
Don't I know it.
我巴不得自己痛痛快快地去了
Mate, I've wished myself dead more times than I can count.
可我还没死
And now here I am,
我想要更多的时间
and I want some more time.
虽然我的时间不多了
But I don't have it,
我没有时间慢慢地告诉你这件事
and I don't have time to ease you into this.
你必须杀了他 比利
You're gonna have to kill him, Billy.
你不能再回沃特塔了
You can't go back to the tower.
你需要和格蕾丝阿姨离开 什么?
You need to go with Aunt Grace.What?
什么时候?现在 马上就走 不 不行
Like when?Now.Right now.No, I-I can't.
我爸会找到我的 这次不会的 孩子
My dad would find me.Not this time, kiddo.
可是
Well...
我不确定自己想离开
I'm not sure I want to leave.
我有点喜欢那里 喜欢某一部分
I kind of like it there. Well, parts of it.
看到了吧?你得把病毒打入他的身体 今天就打
You see?You got to stab him with the virus and you got to do it today.
莱恩 不
Ryan, no.
你爸是一个 格蕾丝
Your Dad is a...Grace.
听着
Look...
你妈去世不是你的错 她离世时说的话
when your mom died... which weren't your fault...
你也听到了
...you heard what she said.
她让我承诺会保证你的安全 我正在兑现承诺
She had me promise to keep you safe, and that's all I'm trying to do here.
如果你告诉我 我是说 严肃地告诉我
Now, if you're telling me,I mean, seriously telling me,
和祖国人在一起让你感觉最安全
that the place you feel safest is with Homelander...
那我不会阻止你
...then I ain't gonna stop you.
你想玩吗?
Do you want to play?
那好吧 来吧
All right, then. Come on.
《静水流深》 深海的诗
你见到莱恩了吗?没有
Have you seen Ryan?No, but I can send a PA
但如果你需要 我可以让制片助理去找找看
to go look, if you need.No. No. Boys need their space.
不用了
男孩子需要自己的空间
清单呢?对不起
List?Oh, yeah. Um... Sorry.
先生 我用萤光笔标记出的人 跟我们签了赔偿合同 如果他们
Thank you.I highlighted anyone who's contract，we'd have to pay out if they're...
被辞退
...let go.
好 谢谢 做得好
Great. Thank you. Good job.
你去吧
You're excused.
没问题 我能冲进去
You know, no problem. I can get it.
香菜口味
Cilantro.
先生们 超级七人队的成员彼此信任
Gentlemen.The Seven is a circle of trust.
我们要告诉各位的信息极其敏感
What we're gonna tell you is extremely sensitive.
懂吗?听您指示 队长
Got it?O Captain, my Captain.
这事一完 罗伯特辛格尔就得死
Robert Singer will be dead by end of business.
纽曼将宣誓就职
Neuman will be sworn in.
大众会恐慌 将会发生骚乱
People will panic. There will be rioting,
流血 等等
bloodshed, et cetera, et cetera.
必须有人快速行动 恢复秩序
Someone will have to swoop in and restore order.
我们将号召每一位沃特英雄 每一位都
We will put out the call to every Vought hero,
他妈的包括在内 包围国会大厦
every fucking one, to surround the Capitol,
白宫和五角大楼
the White House, and the Pentagon.
扞卫合法选举出的总统纽曼
Defending the rightful President Neuman.
现在 我需要你们两个
Now, what I need you two...
真他妈的 吃块止咳糖
Fuck's sakes, get a Ricola.
对不起 先生 我非常抱歉 我只是 是服药导致的 你知道吧
Sorry, sir. I'm-I'm so sorry. I'm just... the meds, you know.
你知道的 那种药
You know, the... the meds.
会引发轻度心悸
They're just, they're causing a little
还有高烧 但这不是什么大事
heart palpitation and a high fever, but it ain't no big thing.
你一咳嗽 飞沫溅得我满身都是 真恶心
Okay, well, you're coughing all over me, and it's fucking disgusting.
往远点坐可以吗
Go further down.
挪一边去
Scoot.
好的
再远点
Further.
正如我所说
As I was saying...
今天 这份清单上的每个人都需要
...everyone on this list needs to be removed.
永远地被清除掉
Permanently, by the end of the day.
如果考虑掌握我们污点信息的人
Hey, if we're thinking about who's got the most dirt on us,
艾诗丽不是应该首当其冲被清除吗?
wouldn't Ashley's name be at the top of the list?
当然 好主意
Yeah. Sure. Good idea.
有人知道艾诗丽姓什么吗?
Does anybody know Ashley's last name?
怎么
What the...?
公共工程部
你说变形者可以通过这扇门 不会吧
You seriously telling us the Shifter can get through that?
据我所知 他们可能已经潜入这里了
Look, for all I fucking know, they could be in here already.
所以 从现在开始 每个人都要结伴行动
So, from now on, everybody moves with a partner,
每五分钟准时检查一次
and you check in every five minutes on the dot.
精神点 听从命令
Stay sharp and follow motherfucking orders.
来吧 开始吧
Come on, let's get to it.
先生 您会没事的
Sir, you're gonna be all right.
如果你们按照我的命令杀了纽曼
If you'd killed Neuman like I ordered,
我们就不会被困在地下四层
we wouldn't be stuck four stories underground
玩袖珍高尔夫球了 白痴
playing pocket pool, idiot.
该死
Balls.
喜美子 贴身保护辛格尔
Kimiko, stay on Singer.
你真的认为变形者在这里吗?
Do you really think the Shifter is in here?
我希望不会 看在上帝的份上 但变形者可以变成任何人
I hope not, for Christ's sake, but it could be anyone,
所以 留意所有人的举动
so eyes on everyone.
没问题
Okay. You got it.
天哪
Jesus.
你还好吗?还好 我很好
You okay?Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
我只是 有点热
I'm just... warm.
这里热得像个熔炉
It's like a furnace in here.
里面热得像个熔炉
It's like a furnace in there.
你去弄点水喝吧
Y-You should go find some water.
好 你想要一瓶吗?
Yeah. Okay. Do you want one?
好啊
I would love one.
我马上就回来 好的
I'll be right back.Okay.
他妈的
Holy fucking shit.
该死
Balls.
伙计 对不起 这事有点蠢
Hey. Hey, man. Hey, just... sorry. Just something... stupid.
不过很快就会说完 别面向我 面向房间
Real quick, just don't look at me, look right into the room.
别面向我 面向房间
Huh?Don't look at me, just look forward.
别面向我 面向房间 好吧
Don't look at me, just look forward.All right, all right, okay.
保持冷静
Stay cool.
是安妮 什么是安妮?
It's Annie.What's Annie?
变形者 是安妮 她是变形者 什么?
The Shifter, it's Annie.What?
别面向我 面向房间
She's the Shifter. Don't look at me, just look forward.
你怎么知道?
How do you know?
相信我就是了 我不知道变形是何时发生 如何发生的
Just trust me, I don't know how or when they switched, but that is
但那边的肯定不是安妮 好吧 听着
100% percent not Annie.Okay, okay, okay, listen.
国家的命运依赖于我们 保持冷静 所以 冷静
The fate of the country relies on us keeping our shit together, so just chill...
嘿!嘿!嘿!
Hey.Hey.Hey.
要水吗?
Water?
谢谢 给你
Thanks.There you go.
很好
Yeah, great.Mm-hmm.
你看什么呢?
What are you looking at?
我知道
Uh...I know.
你
Oh. Wow... you...
恭喜!谢谢
Congratulations.Thank you.
是的 我们结婚了
Yep. We did that.
我们做了那件事
That is a thing...
郑重声明 是我求的婚
that we did.For the record,
让父权制见鬼去好了 对吗?
I proposed. 'Cause peg the patriarchy, right?
对 让父权制见鬼去好了 对 让它见鬼
Yeah, peg the patriarchy. You got to peg it...
见所有的鬼
peg it in all its holes.
结婚 我一生中做过的最棒的决定
Listen, getting hitched,best decision I ever made in my life,
祝贺你们俩
so congratulations to you both.
但 你知道 我得去趟卫生间
But, uh, you know, Mother Nature's calling,
所以 我这就去卫生间
so I'm about to go hit the head, and...
你们坚守堡垒吧 可算中了!
y'all just hold down the fort...Yes, motherfucker.
天哪!先生 跟我来
Sir, get down.Sir, come with me.
先生 这边走
Sir, this way.
完了
Oh, shit.
真他妈的!
Oh, goddamn it.
快走!
快!
Go.
快点!
Come on.
密码怎么这么长?
How many fucking numbers are there?
天哪
Oh, God.
带辛格尔走!快!快走!
Take Singer. Go.Now.
我们走!快!
Let's go.Go.
休伊 走
Hughie, go.
你真的认为自己 负伤后还能打得过我吗?
You really think your broke-down ass can take me?
你连自己都解决不掉 不是吗?
You couldn't even blast yourself out, could you?
你说得对
You're right.
我不知道我是否是英雄
I don't know if I'm a hero.
我他妈不知道自己是谁
I don't know who the fuck I am.
但我确实知道 我他妈的会好好教训你
But I do know that I'm the bitch beating your ass.
维多利亚
Victoria.
辛格尔还活着 你的刺客失败了“失败”?
Singer's alive. Your assassin failed.
现在 中情局会更严密地保护他
What do you mean failed?Now the CIA's gonna find an even deeper hole to hide him in.
可新闻里什么都没报道
Well, there's nothing on the news.
他会悄悄地回击我
Because he's gonna hit me back quietly, and I'm fairly
我确信他有办法做到这一点
fucking sure he has the means to do it.
智者在哪里?
Where is Sage?
或许她能找到办法 收拾你给我们搞的这堆烂摊子
Maybe she can find a way out of this idiotic mess you've dropped us in.
我们还没有失败 如果有必要的话 我会亲自解决辛格尔
We have not failed. I will end Singer myself if I have to.
你将成为总统 然后 你要对我言听计从
You will be president, and you will go along with every word I say
就好像我手里 抓着每一条控制你的提线
as if my hand was jammed up your tight, puckered little asshole,
你要一直像木偶一样受我摆布
like the puppet you've always been.
维多利亚 如果你有一丝一毫的反抗举动
And, Victoria, if you stray even an inch off that path,
我会确保佐伊余生都活得生不如死
I will make sure Zoe knows nothing but pain for the rest of her life,
你的余生里
and I will send you a piece of her every year
每年我都会寄给你她身体的某一部分
for the fucking rest of yours.
没有什么失败!
There is no fail.
猜猜谁是强手中的强手
Well, guess who has two thumbs
他妈的天才中的天才?
and is the motherfucking genius of all fucking geniuses.
病毒制好
The virus is...
你们怎么了?
What happened to you guys?
没关系
你好呀
Hello, hello.
你还好吗?
Um, you okay?
我很好
I'm great.
感谢上帝 你挺身而出
Thank God you showed up.
你是怎么找到我们的?手机定位应用
How'd you find us, anyway?Find Your Phone.
我也找到了你的未婚妻
I actually also found your fiancee.Oh...
恭喜 不 她不是
Congratulations.No, she's not...
她不是我的未婚妻 不 你才是
She wasn't my fiancee.No, you're...
你把戒指戴在了她的手指上 休伊
You put the ring on her finger, Hughie.
我知道 因为她死后 我把它从手指上撬了下来!
Mm.I know because I pried it off her fucking dead hand!
我以为我要跟你订婚 她的样子跟你一模一样
Look, I thought I was getting engaged to you, all right?
连那里的雀斑都丝毫不差
She looked just like you, you know, right down to that freckle you have
所以 你确实干了她
down...So you did fuck her.
我的意思是 你知道 多少次?
I...I mean, you know...How many times?
肯定少于
Had to be less than...
20次
...20.
天哪 我才离开了十天而已
Oh, my fucking God.I was gone for ten days.She almost
都是她主动的 再说一次 怎么夸大这一点都不过分
always initiated, and, again, I cannot overstate this enough,
我以为是你来着
I thought it was you.
只要有人跟你上床 你才不会仔细看呢
Yeah, and as long as you were getting laid, you didn't look too close.
你想要的是那样的安妮
That's the Annie you want.
什么时候都肯给你口交 完美的女孩
Down to go down whenever. The perfect girl.
不是一个抑郁的人 没有历经磨难
Not someone who is depressed or fucked-up
也没有伴有任何并发症
or comes with any complications.
你想知道我怎么知道那不是你吗?
You want to know how I knew it wasn't you?
在公寓里 她穿着设计师款的礼服
In the apartment she wore some designer dress,
而你一到家就会脱下胸罩 换上运动衫
and you always ditch your bra for sweats as soon as you get home.
她一下子就找到了你的车钥匙
She, she found your car keys
而你每次找车钥匙都得找15分钟以上
on the first try, and you have never, ever found your car keys in under 15 minutes.
但终极线索是什么呢?
But the final clue:
在地堡里 她满头大汗
in the bunker she was sweating,
而你总得裹着羊绒披肩
and you have always been and always will be 90% pashmina.
我爱你这一点
I love that about you.
你所有奇怪的 令人惊奇的反常行为 它们是你的独特之处
All your weird, amazing fucked-up-ness, that's what makes you you.
安妮 求你了
Annie, please.
不
I can't.
他妈的
Fuck.
维琪?
Vicky?
我不想继续下去了
I want out.
抱歉 这是 这是开玩笑吗?
Sorry, is-is this a joke?
不是
No.
太过火了
It's gone too far.
你这么说是因为刺杀失败了
No. No, you're just saying that 'cause the assassination failed.
不 我这么说是因为它永远不会结束
No, I'm saying it 'cause it'll never fucking end.
祖国人完全失控了 甚至连智者的话也不听了
Homelander's unhinged, he's not even listening to Sage anymore.
如果当上总统 我就会成为傀儡
If I become president, I'm just gonna be a puppet,
如果我反抗 他就会
and if I fight back, he'll...
我会自愿辞职
I'll resign without a fight.
你需要让中情局 停止对我的调查 帮我和佐伊离开
You just need to get the CIA off my ass and get me and Zoe out.
好吧 滚蛋吧
Okay, fuck all the way off.
你就像那个喊狼来了的混蛋
You're like the asshole who cried wolf.
你做过那么多令人不齿的事
I mean, the shit that you have done...Oh, what?
像你们逼萨米尔造出更多病毒 杀死我那样令人不齿吗?
Like how you got Sameer to cook up some more of the virus to kill me?
还他妈的砍掉他的腿?
Oh, and, yeah, cut off his fucking leg!
很高兴你们两个联系上了 腿不是我砍的
Glad you two connected. Okay.So the leg thing wasn't me,
你并没有留给我们什么选择的空间
and you didn't exactly leave us with a ton of options.
听着 重点是 你攻击我 我还击 这种循环永远不会结束
Look, the point is, you hit me, I hit you back,and it never fucking ends.
战争游戏 休伊
WarGames, Hughie.
唯一的获胜方法就是不玩
The only way to win is not to play.
我以为我想要从政
I thought I wanted this.
不是为了佐伊 也不是为了艾德加 而是为了我
Not for Zoe or...Edgar but for me.
你知道 我只是 我想要安全感
You know, I just... I wanted to feel safe, and not like
不再做红河集体之家里 那个被吓破胆的孩子
that scared fucking kid at Red River.
但我没有安全感 我真的很害怕
But I don't feel safe, and I'm really fucking scared.
我不要因此把佐伊害死
And I'm not getting Zoe killed over this.
这是唯一的办法
This is the only way.
维琪 我不知道该不该相信你
Vicky, I don't know how to trust you.
我会告诉你佐伊在哪里
I'll tell you where Zoe is.
她还好吗?
Is she okay?
是的 但如果我去接她 就会引起太多的关注
Yeah, but if I get her, it'll draw too much attention.
这样 你就知道自己可以信任我了
And that's how you know you can trust me,
因为我放心地把女儿托付给你
because I am trusting my daughter with you.
拜托 休伊
Please, Hughie.
你现在是全世界我唯一可以求助的人
You're literally the only person on Earth I can turn to right now.
别他妈的跑了
Enough fucking running.
对不起 兄弟 你在名单上
Sorry, bro, you're on the list.
别杀我 我可以付钱给你
Don't kill me. I can pay you.
你是个写剧本的 你拿不到任何报酬 拜托
You're a writer.You don't get paid shit.Please...
要我做什么都行
I-I'll do anything.
什么都行?
Anything?
告诉我 我是超级七人队里 最聪明的超级英雄
Tell me I'm the smartest superhero in The Seven.
到目前为止 你是超级七人队里最聪明的超级英雄
You are, by far, the smartest superhero in The Seven.
你很聪明 是个天才
You're brilliant, a genius.
说你最尊重我 当然 除了祖国人之外
And that you respect me the most. Besides Homelander, of course.
当然 我当然尊重你
Of course. Of course I respect you.
你 你超凡脱俗
You-You're amazing.
你这么说只是因为害怕
You're just saying that 'cause you're scared, aren't you?
不 不是的
No, I'm not.
我发誓你就是
I swear.Yeah, you are.
但你知道吗 兄弟?
But you know what, bro?
对我来说 这已经足够了
That's good enough for me.
你看到艾诗丽了吗?
Yo, have you seen Ashley?
这就是艾诗丽
This is Ashley.
不 兄弟 另一个艾诗丽
No, bro.The other Ashley.
这个艾诗丽甚至都不在名单上
This Ashley's not even on the list.Well, I don't know.
那我就不知道了 这里的每个人都他妈的叫艾诗丽
Everyone here's named fucking Ashley.
兄弟
Bro.
杀戮勃起
Murder boner.
你一定是在开玩笑吧
You've got to be kidding me.Look,
如果我们能策反纽曼 以她的强大超能力
if we can flip Neuman, as powerful as she is,
还有她掌握的沃特污点信息
with everything that she has on Vought, I mean,
哪怕只有百分之五的机会
if there's even a five percent chance.
怎么 轻描淡写地忘记 纽曼是个怪物?
Alors, what, just forget that Neuman is a monster?
我没那么说 我是说
I'm not saying that. I'm saying...
我们都干过坏事
Look, we've all done bad shit.
如果她也像我们一样 历尽磨难 饱受痛苦
What if she's just fucked-up like the rest of us,
只是想为自己的孩子创造条件呢?
just trying to do right by her kid?
我们居然在讨论这事 这已经很令人难以置信了
It's insane that we're even discussing this.
令人难以置信的是对于每个问题 我们的解决方案都是谋杀
What's insane is that our solution to every problem is murder.
以前一看到血 我就会害怕
I used to freak out whenever I saw blood.
现在 我连眼皮都不会眨一下
Now I barely blink at it.
不应该是这样的 这不是什么他妈的沃特电影
It shouldn't be that way.This isn't some fucking Vought movie.
暴力不是勇敢 恨我妈也不是
Violence isn't brave.Neither is hating my mom
恨火车头 恨任何人都不是
or A-Train or...anyone.
但原谅 释怀 怀有一丝怜悯之心
But forgiveness,letting go,a little fucking mercy...
那才是勇敢
that's brave.
这很疯狂 但也很勇敢
It's crazy.But it's brave.
我爸教给我的最后一件事 我只是想
It's about the last thing my dad ever taught me, and I just think...
如果我们要战胜怪物 就得开始展现出人性
...if we're ever gonna win against monsters,I think we need to start acting human.
那就做吧
Fuck it.
真的吗?就“那就做”吗?
Really?Just... fuck it?
安妮 我们可能横竖都是死
Annie, we're probably dead either way.
还不如昂首挺胸地搏一次
Might as well go out with our heads held high.
所以 那就做吧
So...fuck it.Oh.
很好
Great.
听着 尝试策反火车头?
Look,taking a chance with A-Train,
简直疯狂至极
that shit was crazy.
但看看结果如何
But look at how it turned out.
真他妈的
Shit.
那就做吧
Fuck it.
休伊 如果你错了
Petit Hughie,if you're wrong...
信任 但要验证
Trust but verify.
话说回来 法兰奇 你能给纽曼注射病毒吗?
But, Frenchie, can you get that virus into Neuman's system?
用带有碳超材料尖端的飞镖枪
With a carbon metamaterial tip to a dart gun
我会瞄准软组织
and I aim for soft tissue...
也许吧 那就去吧
...perhaps.Then do it.
因为如果这是个陷阱 至少我们没有盲目地跳进去
'Cause if this is a trap, at least we ain't walking in blind.
而且 休伊 如果纽曼有一丝一毫不对劲
And, Hughie, if Neuman even blinks funny,
弗兰奇就会干掉她 很公平 明白
Frenchie's dropping her.Fair. Got it.
听着 我们需要 住口
Look, Annie...Shut up.
你要去检查每一种已知的 人类会得的疾病
You are getting tested for every single disease known to mankind.
好吗?
Okay?
我可不想被感染上梅毒
I'm not getting Shifter syphilis.
太他妈的好了 休伊!太他妈的好了!
Fuck yeah, Hughie. Fuck yeah.
你真的认为这样做是明智的吗?
You really think this is wise?
如果休伊是对的呢?
What if Hughie's right?
如果宽恕是 我们能做的最好的事情呢?
What if forgiveness is the best we can do?
连纽曼都能宽恕?
Even to Neuman?
宽恕纽曼
To Neuman.
也宽恕我们自己
To ourselves.
与我们相比 宽恕纽曼很容易 对吧?
Neuman is easy compared to us.
怎么做?
How?
我想我们可以每天都做出一点尝试
We try a little every day, I guess.
你记得我之前说 你应该和科林在一起吗?
You know how I said you should be with Colin?
我撒了谎
I lied.
我只是觉得你值得
I just thought you deserved to be with someone...
跟比我好的人
Better than me.
在一起
Mon coeur...
没有人
...there is no one...
比你更好
...better than you.
你们知道我能听到
You know I can hear you.
“马文说有人意图 刺杀辛格尔
"Marvin said there was an attempt on Singer's life.
没得手”我们知道 只是你不用担心这些事 仅此而已
He survived."We know.There's just some things you don't got to worry about. That's all.
他们还会再次尝试
They're gonna try again, and that virus
那种病毒是仅存的希望
is a Hail Mary at best.
我们没时间了 也没有更好的选择
We are out of time and out of better options.
莱恩需要知道真相
Ryan needs to know the truth.
会告诉他的 什么真相?
And we'll get there.What truth?
意图暗杀总统 是你父亲下的命令
The assassination attempt,it was on your father's orders.
什么?
What?
还有37号航班
And Flight 37...
飞机上的每一个人都是祖国人杀死的
Homelander killed every soul on board.
格蕾丝
Grace.
你在说谎 我们有视频为证
You're lying.We have it on video.
还有无数其他的人也惨遭他的毒手
And he's murdered countless more.
你父亲并不是你想像的那样 别说了
Your father isn't who you think he is.Just stop.
他并没跟你妈发生婚外恋 格蕾丝!
And he wasn't having an affair with your mother.Grace.
他强奸了她!
He raped her.
对不起 孩子
I'm sorry, son.
然后呢?
And?
你的心在狂跳 你有事瞒着我
Your heart's pounding.There's something you're not telling me.
唯一能阻止他的人就是你
And you're the only one who can stop him.
阻止他?
S-Stop him?
你是说杀了他吗?
Like, kill him?
不 我下不去手
No. No, I can't.
别让我去
Don't ask me to.
莱恩 你很强大
Ryan, you're strong.
他更强大!我们会训练你
He's stronger.We'll train you.
让你做好准备 你们想让我跟你们一起走 是为了这个目的吗?
Get you ready.So this is why you want me to go with you?
这样 你们就能教我 如何杀掉我生父?
So you can teach me how to kill my dad?
我得走了 留下来
I have to go.No, just stay.
我们会一起讨论 我不想讨论
We'll talk it out together.I don't want to talk.
我会回来的 我只是需要思考
I'll be back, I just need to think.
听着 伙计 不会再有下次了
Listen, Ryan, there ain't gonna be another time for you and me.
我们暂时先冷静下 好吗?你不能离开
All right?Let's just take a breather. Yeah?You can't leave.
等等
Wait.
这些墙有近两米厚
These walls are six feet thick.
这是中情局的黑兹莱特安全屋
This is the CIA's Hazlet safe house.
旨在关住你这样的人
Designed to hold people like you.
我可以把我们封死在这里 用氟烷充满房间
I could seal us in here, flood the room with halothane.
我们都美美地睡个一睡不醒的觉
And we all take a nice, long nap.
但我不想那样做 孩子 你们早有预谋
But I don't want to do that, kiddo.You planned this.
你们把我带到这里来是为了困住我
All along. You, you brought me here to trap me.
不 我们带你来这里是为了帮助你
No, no. We brought you here to help you.
除非我同意为你们杀人 否则 你们就会把我关在这里!
You're locking me in a cage unless I agree to be your weapon.
就像他们对我父亲那样 事实并非如此 老实说
Just like they did to my dad.That ain't the way it is, honest.
让我走 莱恩 失去孙子时
Let me go.Ryan.When I lost my grandkids, it left
我内心空空如也 丧失了全部的希望
this big empty black hole inside me.
可最伟大的奇迹出现了
Then the greatest miracle came along.
你
You.
我爱你 孩子
I love you, kiddo.
求你了
Please.
格蕾丝 我想离开
Aunt Grace... I want to leave.
对不起 别挡我的路
I'm sorry.Get out of my way.
格蕾丝 抱歉
Grace.I'm sorry.
不!
No!
什么?
What?
我们进来了
Hello, hello.
上次见面后 你把牙套摘下来了
You took your braces off, since last time we saw you.
我们别搞这套
Let's not do that.Uh-huh.
纽曼 要怎么做?
How's this gonna work, Neuman?
简单
Simple.
你们帮我摆脱祖国人 还有辛格尔在中情局的人
You help me get clear of Homelander,and Singer's people at the CIA.
我悄无声息地走人
And I go quietly.Mm.
你欠我们一份人情 不止一份人情
And you'll owe us one.A lot more than one.
我会欠你们很多人情
I will owe you many.
很好 所以 你会帮我们打倒沃特
Great. So you're gonna help us take down Vought
还有祖国人
and Homelander.
布彻尔?
Butcher?
没有交易可做
No deals.
我可以解释 好吗?没事的 我知道
I can explain, all right?It's all good. I know
这看起来是什么样 我们以前经历过那么多事
what this looks like, but with everything that we've been through together,
我从没有要求过你相信我 这一次 我要你信任我
I've never once asked you to trust me. I am asking now.
就像你过去信任莱尼一样
Like the way you used to trust Lenny.
拜托了 布彻尔
Please, Butcher.
住手!
Stop!
不
No, no, no, no.
别动!
Stop. Stop.
这是自杀
It's suicide.
病毒给我 谢谢 法兰奇
I'll be taking that virus now, thanks, Frenchie.
绝对不行
Ain't no fucking way.
你注射了五号
You took V?
它也会干掉你
It will work on you, too.
如果我是你们 就不会犹豫不决
If I were you lot,I wouldn't hang about.
顺便说一句
Oh, by the way.
不用谢
You're all fucking welcome.
突发新闻 据报道 白宫处于封锁状态
We are interrupting our regular reporting with a breaking news story,
插播一条突发新闻
对不起 我只是
that at... I'm sorry, I'm just
在看制作人 已被证实了吗?
looking to my producers here. Is this confirmed?
他们 他们告诉我消息已被证实
They're, they're, they're telling me it has been.
当选副总统 维多利亚纽曼去世了
The Vice President-Elect, Victoria Neuman, is dead.
全世界知晓她是超人类之后
Assassinated today only hours
才过了几个小时 她就被暗杀了
after revealing to the world that she is super-abled...
莱恩在哪里?
Where's Ryan?
毕竟这些都是为了他 对吗?
This was all for him after all, right?
你来这里做什么?庆祝
What are you doing here?Celebrating.
我们赢了 给
We won. Here.
一切都毁了 计划未能奏效
Everything's turned to shit.Plan's dead.
这就是计划
This is the plan.
当然 略有偏差 但我们达成了目标
I mean, sure, a few curveballs,but, uh, we got here.
不能将计划全盘托出而已
Just had to keep a few bits to myself.
让你毁掉的那部分
You know, the bits you'd fuck up by...
你知道 你就是那种人嘛
...you know, being you.
纽曼本来就是个可怜虫 固执 想法太多
Neuman would have been a shit patsy.Stubborn, too many ideas.
所以 我选择了另一种方法
So I went another way.
鲍勃辛格本人下的暗杀令
...Bob Singer himself ordering the assassination.
如果你们按照我的命令杀了纽曼
If you'd killed Neuman like I ordered,
我们就不会被困在地下四层 玩袖珍高尔夫球了
we wouldn't be stuck four stories underground playing pocket pool.
现在 我们开始直播
And now we go live.
您看到的画面是当选总统罗伯特辛格
Okay, that's President-Elect Robert Singer taken into custody by federal agents...
被联邦特工拘留
She tried to kill me first.
在史无前例的事态转变中
...in an unprecedented turn of events that is
那肯定是最为黑暗的日子之一
certain to go down as one of the darkest days...
找你的
It's for you.
是谁?卡尔霍恩众议院议长
Who is it?Oh, Speaker of the House Calhoun.
一旦援引第25号修正案 他就是下一个总统候选人
Once they invoke the 25th,he's next in line to be president.
他想向你宣誓效忠
He'd like to pledge his allegiance to you.
向我?
To me?
就像我承诺的那样
Just like I promised.
我们说好的
We had a deal.
是的 我破坏了协议
Yeah, well, I broke the deal.
我没有
I didn't.
我告诉过你 你可以相信我 亲爱的
I told you,you could trust me, boo.
我支持你
I got your back.
但我 把你赶了出去 就像 你是
I-I threw you out like...
垃圾
...like garbage.
你为什么要这样做?
Why would you do this?
看看我是否做得到
To see if I could.
谢谢
Thank you.
太有趣了
This was so much fun.
只是 你知道 下次
Just, you know, next time,
听我的
listen to me.
下次?
Next time?
没错 金发野心家!
Oh, hells yeah, blond ambition.
准备好 进入第二阶段
Buckle up for phase two.
我是祖国人
Homelander speaking.
因此 作为我的第一项正式动议
And that is why, as my first official act,
根据《宪法》第九条第一款
under Article One, Section Nine of the Constitution,
我宣布戒严
I'm declaring martial law
代表数百名全国范围内的 超级英雄宣布
and deputizing hundreds of superheroes nationwide,
他们将直接向祖国人汇报
who will report directly to Homelander himself.
以保持 谢谢您 总统先生
To keep...Thank you, Mr. President.
维多利亚纽曼 她是一个伟大的美国人
Victoria Neuman, she was a great American.
也是一位亲爱的朋友
And a dear, dear friend.
被潜伏进我国政府的 暗黑势力集团的星光追随者
Murdered in cold blood by deep-state Starlighters
冷血谋杀了
embedded in our own government.
现在 我们拥有完全的合法权力
Now that we have full legal authority,
一支名副其实的 超级英雄军队将被召唤
a veritable army of superheroes will be called upon
把这些叛徒从我们的政府中 以及街道上赶出去
to rout these traitors from our government and from our streets.
美国将再度变得安全起来
America will be safe again.
对星光追随者们说两句 无论你们躲在哪里
And to the Starlighters,whatever rock you're hiding under,
我们很快就会找到你们
we're coming for you.
我会找到你们
I'm coming for you.
因为今天
Because today...
超人类英雄的新时代开始了
...a new age of superheroes begins.
一觉醒来 我们的世界焕然一新
We wake up to a new world.
这里充满希望 纯洁 耶稣的爱照耀着我们所有人
Where hope, purity and Jesus's love shine down upon us all.
孩子们可以在母亲的怀抱中安然睡去
Where children can sleep peacefully in their mothers' arms,
因为他们知道 星光的恋童计划已被挫败
knowing Starlight's pedo agenda has been thwarted.
红河集体之家
不好 不!
喜美子!
Kimiko!
在这里 美国终于看到了 觉醒暴民的真面目
Where America finally sees the woke mob
他们是想要摧毁我们优良传统的怪物
for what it is: monsters who want to destroy
拐卖我们的孩子 促使我国男性女性化的怪物
our heritage, traffic our children,and feminize our men.
在祖国人的领导下
Where, with Homelander's guidance...
我们将团结一致
...we will all come together in unity.
不!
No.
不!不!
No. No!
不!
No!
我们将使美国再次强大起来
We will make America strong again.
再次骄傲起来
Proud again.
最重要的是 超人类将再次驾驭美国
And most of all,we will make America super again.
你知道多久了?
How long have you known?
今天早上在机密报告会上才得知
Only since this morning's classified briefing.
我立即就联系了你
You were my first call.
向上帝发誓
Hand to God.
开什么玩笑
You got to be fucking kidding me.
居然一直都在这里?
This whole time.
献给拉里·克里普克